isme.com 2007-11-20

# Privacy

|  | 

**Let's Work Together,**

**To Achieve** **Real Results!!**

**Stephen Conley**

 Licensed Real Estate 

Broker Associate

42 Crown Street

Kingston, NY 12401

  |   | 

I recognizes that respecting user privacy over the Internet is of utmost importance. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site:  http://www.isme.com. The Site is operated by  Stephen Conley.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our site coordinator at stephen@isme.com or by postal mail to:

  * Looking Glass Realty, LLC
  * Atten. Stephen Conley
  * 418 First Avenue
  * Kingston, NY 12401

Identifying Information. In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to offer services that require registration, to follow up with you. Generally, we requests identifying information when you: 

  * Register on any of our web sites. 
  * Provide feedback to an online survey or tell us about an idea or suggestion. 
  * Request a SPECIAL SERVICE
  * Request additional information on listings

In these instances, you will be asked for your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and other appropriate information needed to provide you with these services. In all instances, if you receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.

What we Will Do With Your Information. If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by us and will only be used by us to support your customer or client relationship. We will not add you to a mailing list, or newsletter without your registration for this service. We will only contact you if further information is required from you to complete a service.

We do not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through our Site (such as your name or email address) to any outside organization for use in its marketing or solicitations. All personal information is confidential and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services we provide to our customers and clients. In addition, we may also share aggregate information about its customers and its web site visitors to advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we might share that our users are x percent PCs users and y percent Macintosh users. None of this information, however, will contain personal, identifying information about our customers or clients. 

## Third Party Links

[isme.com](http://www.isme.com/) ulsterrealestate.net and stephenconley.com  all provide links to other sites. Other Internet sites and services have separate privacy and data collection practices. Once you leave our site we are not in control, and have no responsibility for, the privacy policies or data collection activities at another site. 

## Cookies 

At times, we will use a feature on your web browser to send your computer a "cookie". We do not use cookies to retrieve any personal information from your computer. We only use cookies to learn ways to enhance our Sites, and to give you better, more personalized service while in our web site. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is sent. However, some functions of the Sites will not function if you refuse cookies. These areas of our web site will have information posted about cookies, and when a cookie will be uploaded to your computer.

## Children's Privacy Protection

We are sensitive to the heightened need to protect the privacy of children. Our site is intended for adults age 18 and older looking to buy and sell real estate. The vast majority of the material on our web site is not intended for children and is not targeted to children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect data from children and, if we learn that we have received personal data from a child, we will remove this information from our database. 

## Changes to this Policy

We may from time to time revise our privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.   
Contacting Us. If you have any questions about our privacy policy and/or the practices of our web site visit the Contact Page. 

* * *

**Serving Ulster County's Real Estate Needs**

|    
---|---|---|---|---
